const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of these diseases is associated with complete monosomy?","answers":[{"option":"Ebstein anomaly","bool":false},{"option":"Gastrochisis","bool":false},{"option":"Umbilical hernia","bool":false},{"option":"Coarctation of aorta","bool":true},{"option":"Tetralogy of Fallot","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of these medications can be used orally for scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Lindane","bool":false},{"option":"Benzoyl benzoate","bool":false},{"option":"Permethrin","bool":false},{"option":"Ivermectin","bool":true},{"option":"Malathion","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is the most important treatment for body louse?","answers":[{"option":"Washing clothing","bool":true},{"option":"5% permethrin","bool":false},{"option":"25% benzoyl benzoate","bool":false},{"option":"Ivermectin","bool":false},{"option":"1% permethrin","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"A person is brought out of a smoke-filled room in an unconscious state. Which poisoning is suspected?","answers":[{"option":"Carbon monoxide","bool":true},{"option":"Oxygen","bool":false},{"option":"Nitrogen dioxide","bool":false},{"option":"Carbon dioxide","bool":false},{"option":"Cyanide","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"What is the mode of inheritance of cystic fibrosis?","answers":[{"option":"X-linked recessive","bool":false},{"option":"X-linked dominant","bool":false},{"option":"Mitochondrial inheritence","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal dominant","bool":false},{"option":"Autosomal recessive","bool":true}]},{"id":5,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is not a trinucleotide repeat disorder?","answers":[{"option":"Duchenne muscular dystrophy","bool":true},{"option":"Friedreich ataxia","bool":false},{"option":"Myotonic dystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Huntington disease","bool":false},{"option":"Fragile X syndrome","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of the following is true about Huntington disease?","answers":[{"option":"Mutation coding for excess glutamine","bool":true},{"option":"Dominant mutation on chromosome 21","bool":false},{"option":"Dominant mutation on chromosome 16","bool":false},{"option":"Recessive mutation on chromosome 21","bool":false},{"option":"Death before reproductive age","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of the following is associated with Steven-Johnson syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Varicella zoster","bool":false},{"option":"Measles","bool":false},{"option":"Mumps","bool":false},{"option":"Mycoplasma pneumoniae","bool":true},{"option":"Rubella","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of these diseases is common in overcrowded homes?","answers":[{"option":"Anthrax","bool":false},{"option":"Leprosy","bool":false},{"option":"Genital herpes","bool":false},{"option":"Scabies","bool":true},{"option":"Mumps","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these nail findings is common in psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Nail pitting","bool":true},{"option":"Terry's nails","bool":false},{"option":"Splinter hemorrhages","bool":false},{"option":"Leukonychia","bool":false},{"option":"Pterygium","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is the drug of choice in psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Antibiotics","bool":false},{"option":"Selenium sulfide","bool":false},{"option":"Antifungals","bool":false},{"option":"Permethrin","bool":false},{"option":"Topical vitamin D","bool":true}]},{"id":11,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"The variation in skin color among people is due to multiple genes on different loci. What is this phenomenon called?","answers":[{"option":"Monogenic inheritence","bool":false},{"option":"Pleiotropy","bool":false},{"option":"Incomplete dominance","bool":false},{"option":"Polygenic inheritence","bool":true},{"option":"Epistasis","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"What is the professional integration of a person into society to reduce the economic burden called?","answers":[{"option":"Vocational rehabilitation","bool":true},{"option":"Selective placement","bool":false},{"option":"Psychological rehabilitation","bool":false},{"option":"Social rehabilitation","bool":false},{"option":"Social inclusion","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"The term disturbed health status refers to which term?","answers":[{"option":"Functionality","bool":false},{"option":"Mental health","bool":false},{"option":"Handicap","bool":false},{"option":"Impairment","bool":true},{"option":"Disability","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is not an inherited cancer?","answers":[{"option":"Breast cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Prostate cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Colon cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Ovarian cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Sarcoma","bool":true}]},{"id":15,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is a suitable drug for psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Azathioprine","bool":false},{"option":"Fumaric acid derivative","bool":false},{"option":"Crypoterone acetate","bool":false},{"option":"Mycophenolate","bool":false},{"option":"Acitretin","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is not a genetic disease?","answers":[{"option":"Thalassemia","bool":false},{"option":"Phenylketonuria","bool":false},{"option":"Cystic fibrosis","bool":false},{"option":"Cretinism","bool":true},{"option":"Sickle cell disease","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of these is not an invasive prenatal diagnostic test?","answers":[{"option":"Chordocentesis","bool":false},{"option":"Fetal blood sampling","bool":false},{"option":"Amniocentesis","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":true},{"option":"Karyotyping","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of the following disorders is characterized by CAG repeats?","answers":[{"option":"Friedreich ataxia","bool":false},{"option":"Fragile X syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Hungtington disease","bool":true},{"option":"Myotonic dystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Duchenne muscular dystrophy","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of the following disorders is characterized by CTG repeats?","answers":[{"option":"Spinobulbar muscular atrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Myotonic dystrophy","bool":true},{"option":"Fragile X syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Friedreich's ataxia","bool":false},{"option":"Hungtington's disease","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of the following dermatomes is most commonly affected by herpes zoster?","answers":[{"option":"Thoracic","bool":true},{"option":"Trigeminal","bool":false},{"option":"Lumbar","bool":false},{"option":"Cervical","bool":false},{"option":"Sacral","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which one of the following electrolyte abnormalities are caused by amphotericin B?","answers":[{"option":"Hypermagnesemia","bool":false},{"option":"Hyponatremia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypophosphatemia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypocalcemia","bool":false},{"option":"Hypokalemia","bool":true}]},{"id":22,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"Which of the following is a disorder with CTG repeats?","answers":[{"option":"Huntington dystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Fragile X syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Friedrich ataxia","bool":false},{"option":"Beker muscular dystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Myotonic dystrophy","bool":true}]},{"id":23,"info":"4th-year/drg/2016","question":"What is the correct sequence of steps required for blotting?","answers":[{"option":"Gel electrophoresis -> transfer to membrane -> hybridization -> visualization","bool":true},{"option":"Transfer to membrane -> gel electrophoresis -> hybridization -> visualization","bool":false},{"option":"Hybridization -> visualization -> transfer to membrane -> gel electrophoresis","bool":false},{"option":"Gel electrophoresis -> visualization -> transfer to membrane -> hybridization","bool":false},{"option":"Gel electrophoresis -> hybridization -> transfer to membrane -> visualization","bool":false}]}]
export default arr